dreamtripslife.com 2013-11-20

# privacypolicy

Privacy Policy

Rovia.com guarantees that the privacy and security of all personal and/or financial information shared by you will be protected in compliance with the highest e-commerce security standards when exchanged over the internet. The Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology we use ensures the privacy and security of all transactions. SSL technology encrypts data before it is transmitted, so that only the authorized recipient can have access to it. In addition to SSL technology, your information is further protected by the following: segmentation and compartmentalization of information on our network to ensure restricted access to customer information databases; physical and logical barriers to unauthorized access; and a best of breed firewall system. Rovia.com is a trusted VeriSign secure site and uses VeriSign digital certificates with all transactions. Rovia.com's status with VeriSign may be verified independently by visiting the VeriSign website.  
COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION  
This site requires that customers share personal and/or financial information in order to receive the services offered. With the following exceptions, such information will be used strictly for the purposes of providing the services requested:  
1\. Telephone numbers may be used to contact customers in case of an urgent need relating to an existing reservation or request for services.  
2\. E-mail addresses may be used to inform clients of services and offers which are most likely to be of interest to them. With respect to this use of personal information, customers may at any time indicate their preference not to receive such information by sending an email to support@Rovia.com. RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA  
Legal obligations may require that Rovia.com retain personal information for a specified period of time. If so, Rovia.com will only retain personal information for the duration of the specified period. Generic demographic data gleaned from personal information and used for marketing purposes may be retained longer but will be purged of any information which can be used identify customers personally.  
INFORMATION SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIES  
Rovia.com will share your personal information with banks, processing companies, and service providers involved in providing you the services requested. Unless there is an emergency and Rovia.com is legally obliged to do so by law, Rovia.com will never share your personal information with any other third parties.   
VISITOR IP LOGGING  
Rovia.com logs visitor IP addresses to optimize server performance and to track visitor movement through our site. In the case of the latter, the information is used by our web analytics software to provide us with important marketing information about our customers.   
COOKIES  
Upon your initial visit to our site, Rovia.com will automatically set a cookie – a small piece of data– on your hard drive to welcome you back to the site upon subsequent visits and to save your chosen site parameters. We do not use cookies to collect any information other than just described, and the information stored in a cookie can in no way be used to identify you personally. You can always avoid receiving cookies by setting your Web browser to refuse them.   
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES  
This website contains links to third-party websites. Rovia™.com’s Privacy Policy does not apply to these sites, and Rovia.com makes no guarantees as to the privacy policy of any third party sites to which it contains links.   
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY  
Rovia.com may change its Privacy Policy at any time without notice. You agree that any information shared by you in relation to a booking is subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your most recent booking. If you have any questions or concerns regarding any provision of this policy, you are urged to contact us.
